<?xml version="1.0"?>
<CIM CIMVERSION="2.3" DTDVERSION="2.2"><DECLARATION><DECLGROUP><VALUE.OBJECT>
<CLASS SUPERCLASS="CIM_ManagedElement" NAME="CIM_BIOSAttribute"><QUALIFIER TOSUBCLASS="false" TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Version" TYPE="string"><VALUE>2.22.0</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="UMLPackagePath" TYPE="string"><VALUE>CIM::System::BIOS</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A class derived from ManagedElement that provides instrumentation of BIOS configuration data or Attributes of a managed computer system or device. These attributes are surfaced in the form of BIOSAttribute instances. The CIM_BIOSAttribute object may be used to represent both configurable and static BIOS attributes.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BIOSAttribute" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="InstanceID" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TOSUBCLASS="false" NAME="Override" TYPE="string"><VALUE>InstanceID</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Within the scope of the instantiating Namespace, InstanceID opaquely and uniquely identifies an instance of this class. In order to ensure uniqueness within the NameSpace, the value of InstanceID SHOULD be constructed using the following &amp;apos;preferred&amp;apos; algorithm: &lt;OrgID&gt;:&lt;LocalID&gt;Where &lt;OrgID&gt; and &lt;LocalID&gt; are separated by a colon &amp;apos;:&amp;apos;, and where &lt;OrgID&gt; MUST include a copyrighted, trademarked or otherwise unique name that is owned by the business entity creating/defining the InstanceID, or is a registered ID that is assigned to the business entity by a recognized global authority (This is similar to the &lt;Schema Name&gt;_&lt;Class Name&gt; structure of Schema class names.) In addition, to ensure uniqueness &lt;OrgID&gt; MUST NOT contain a colon (&amp;apos;:&amp;apos;). When using this algorithm, the first colon to appear in InstanceID MUST appear between &lt;OrgID&gt; and &lt;LocalID&gt;. &lt;LocalID&gt; is chosen by the business entity and SHOULD not be re-used to identify different underlying (real-world) elements. If the above &amp;apos;preferred&amp;apos; algorithm is not used, the defining entity MUST assure that the resultant InstanceID is not re-used across any InstanceIDs produced by this or other providers for this instance&apos;s NameSpace. For DMTF defined instances, the &amp;apos;preferred&amp;apos; algorithm MUST be used with the &lt;OrgID&gt; set to &amp;apos;CIM&amp;apos;.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BIOSAttribute" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="AttributeName" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Required" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A string identifying the structured element name for a BIOS attribute using the format &quot;&lt;OrgID&gt;:&lt;identifier&gt;&quot; in which &lt;OrgID&gt;, does contain a colon (&quot;:&quot;). The value of &lt;OrgID&gt; is a copyrighted, trademarked or otherwise unique name that is owned by the entity defining the &lt;identifier&gt;, or is a registered ID that is assigned to the entity by a recognized global authority. For DMTF defined identifiers, the &lt;OrgID&gt; is set to &apos;DMTF&apos; and the &lt;identifier&gt; is specified in the BIOS Attribute Registry.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY.ARRAY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BIOSAttribute" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="CurrentValue" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Required" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>An array of strings representing the current value or values of the BIOS Attribute.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY.ARRAY><PROPERTY.ARRAY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BIOSAttribute" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="DefaultValue" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>An array of strings representing the default value or values of the BIOS Attribute.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY.ARRAY><PROPERTY.ARRAY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BIOSAttribute" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="PendingValue" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>An array of strings representing a pending Attribute value that will not take affect until some point in the future. This would typically be used to represent Attributes that could not be changed until a system reset. When a BIOS attribute has no pending changes, PendingValue SHALL be NULL. PendingValue SHALL have a value of at least one element from the CIM_BIOSEnumeration.PossibleValues array when the an instance of the central class represents an enumeration.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY.ARRAY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BIOSAttribute" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="IsOrderedList" TYPE="boolean"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>This property specifies that the Attribute represented makes up an ordered selection list with elements in the CurrentValue array. The element zero shall be first or least numbered element and incrementally increase to the end of the array. The least or first element may represent the highest priority in the ordered list.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ModelCorrespondence" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>CIM_BIOSAttribute.CurrentValue</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BIOSAttribute" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="IsReadOnly" TYPE="boolean"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>This property specifies if the underlying system BIOS or BIOSService will not allow the Attribute to be modified through calls tothe methods CIM_BIOSService.SetBIOSAttribute or CIM_BIOSService.SetBIOSDefaults. This does not mean the Attribute can not be modified through other means. Only that the CIM interfaceis not capable of making a change</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ManagedElement" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="Caption" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The Caption property is a short textual description (one- line string) of the object.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="MaxLen" TYPE="uint32"><VALUE>64</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ManagedElement" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The Description property provides a textual description of the object.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ManagedElement" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="ElementName" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A user-friendly name for the object. This property allows each instance to define a user-friendly name in addition to its key properties, identity data, and description information. 
Note that the Name property of ManagedSystemElement is also defined as a user-friendly name. But, it is often subclassed to be a Key. It is not reasonable that the same property can convey both identity and a user-friendly name, without inconsistencies. Where Name exists and is not a Key (such as for instances of LogicalDevice), the same information can be present in both the Name and ElementName properties. Note that if there is an associated instance of CIM_EnabledLogicalElementCapabilities, restrictions on this properties may exist as defined in ElementNameMask and MaxElementNameLen properties defined in that class.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY></CLASS></VALUE.OBJECT></DECLGROUP></DECLARATION></CIM>
