<?xml version="1.0"?>
<CIM CIMVERSION="2.3" DTDVERSION="2.2"><DECLARATION><DECLGROUP><VALUE.OBJECT>
<CLASS SUPERCLASS="CIM_BasedOn" NAME="CIM_LogicalDiskBasedOnExtent"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Association" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TOSUBCLASS="false" TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Version" TYPE="string"><VALUE>2.6.0</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="UMLPackagePath" TYPE="string"><VALUE>CIM::Device::StorageExtents</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>LogicalDisks can be BasedOn a single StorageVolume, Memory (in the case of a RAM Disk), a DiskPartition or other StorageExtent. These relationships are made explicit in this association. Subclasses of the association, LogicalDiskBasedOn Partition and LogicalDiskBasedOnVolume, detail the &apos;typical&apos; semantics.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><PROPERTY.REFERENCE CLASSORIGIN="CIM_LogicalDiskBasedOnExtent" PROPAGATED="false" REFERENCECLASS="CIM_StorageExtent" NAME="Antecedent"><QUALIFIER TOSUBCLASS="false" NAME="Override" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Antecedent</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="Max" TYPE="uint32"><VALUE>1</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The StorageExtent.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY.REFERENCE><PROPERTY.REFERENCE CLASSORIGIN="CIM_LogicalDiskBasedOnExtent" PROPAGATED="false" REFERENCECLASS="CIM_LogicalDisk" NAME="Dependent"><QUALIFIER TOSUBCLASS="false" NAME="Override" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Dependent</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The LogicalDisk which is built on the StorageExtent.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY.REFERENCE><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BasedOn" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="StartingAddress" TYPE="uint64"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>StartingAddress indicates where in lower level storage, the higher level Extent begins.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BasedOn" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="EndingAddress" TYPE="uint64"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>EndingAddress indicates where in lower level storage, the higher level Extent ends. This property is useful when mapping non-contiguous Extents into a higher level grouping.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_BasedOn" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="OrderIndex" TYPE="uint16"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>If there is an order to the BasedOn associations that describe how a higher level StorageExtent is assembled, the OrderIndex property indicates this. When an order exists, the instances of BasedOn with the same Dependent value (i.e., the same higher level Extent) should place unique values in the OrderIndex property. The lowest value implies the first member of the collection of lower level Extents, and increasing values imply successive members of the collection. If there is no ordered relationship, a value of zero should be specified. An example of the use of this property is to define a RAID-0 striped array of 3 disks. The resultant RAID array is a StorageExtent that is dependent on (BasedOn) the StorageExtents that describe each of the 3 disks. The OrderIndex of each BasedOn association from the disk Extents to the RAID array could be specified as 1, 2 and 3 to indicate the order in which the disk Extents are used to access the RAID data.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY></CLASS></VALUE.OBJECT></DECLGROUP></DECLARATION></CIM>
