<?xml version="1.0"?>
<CIM CIMVERSION="2.3" DTDVERSION="2.2"><DECLARATION><DECLGROUP><VALUE.OBJECT>
<CLASS NAME="CIM_CredentialContext"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Association" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TOSUBCLASS="false" TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Version" TYPE="string"><VALUE>2.27.0</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="UMLPackagePath" TYPE="string"><VALUE>CIM::User::Credential</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>This relationship defines a context (e.g., a System or Service) of a Credential. One example is a shared secret/ password which is defined within the context of an application (or Service). Generally, there is one scoping element for a Credential, however the multiplicities of the association allow a Credential to be scoped by more than one element. If this association is not instantiated for a Credential, that Credential is assumed to be scoped to the Namespace.
This association may also be used to indicate that a Credential is valid in some other environment. For instance associating the Credential to a RemoteServiceAccessPoint would indicate that the Credential is used to access the remote service.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><PROPERTY.REFERENCE CLASSORIGIN="CIM_CredentialContext" PROPAGATED="false" REFERENCECLASS="CIM_Credential" NAME="ElementInContext"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A Credential whose context is defined.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY.REFERENCE><PROPERTY.REFERENCE CLASSORIGIN="CIM_CredentialContext" PROPAGATED="false" REFERENCECLASS="CIM_ManagedElement" NAME="ElementProvidingContext"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The ManagedElement that provides context or scope for the Credential.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY.REFERENCE><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_CredentialContext" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="Usage" TYPE="uint16"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The usage of the certificate by the managed element that the certificate is for or is scoped to. Owned - Credential represents the CredentialContexts identity. This means that the managed element will present this credential to another party for authentication, authorization, or both. Trusted - The ManagedElement trusts the credential. This means that the credential is trusted for one or more of the security operations such as authentication, third-party authentication, and authorization. Trusted for Authentication - The ManagedElement trusts the identity represented by the credential only for authentication purposes. Trusted for Authorization - The ManagedElement trusts the identity represented by the credential only for authorization purposes. Trusted for Authentication/Authorization - The ManagedElement trusts the identity represented by the credential both for authentication and authorization purposes. Trusted for Third-Party Authentication/Authorization - The credential is being trusted for approving a third-party credential to the ManagedElement.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ValueMap" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>2</VALUE><VALUE>3</VALUE><VALUE>4</VALUE><VALUE>6</VALUE><VALUE>7</VALUE><VALUE>8</VALUE><VALUE>..</VALUE><VALUE>32768..65535</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Values" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>Owned</VALUE><VALUE>Trusted</VALUE><VALUE>Trusted for Authentication</VALUE><VALUE>Trusted for Authorization</VALUE><VALUE>Trusted for Authentication/Authorization</VALUE><VALUE>Trusted for Third-Party Authentication/Authorization</VALUE><VALUE>DMTF Reserved</VALUE><VALUE>Vendor Reserved</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY></CLASS></VALUE.OBJECT></DECLGROUP></DECLARATION></CIM>
