<?xml version="1.0"?>
<CIM CIMVERSION="2.3" DTDVERSION="2.2"><DECLARATION><DECLGROUP><VALUE.OBJECT>
<CLASS SUPERCLASS="CIM_ListenerDestination" NAME="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement"><QUALIFIER TOSUBCLASS="false" TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Version" TYPE="string"><VALUE>2.22.0</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="UMLPackagePath" TYPE="string"><VALUE>CIM::Event</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement describes the destination for CIM indications to be delivered via WS-Management.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="Destination" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Required" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TOSUBCLASS="false" NAME="Override" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Destination</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The destination URL defined in the WS-Eventing Subscribe message. This must match the wsa:Address element in the wse:NotifyTo EPR. The value may be the WS-Addressing anonymous URI if the subscription uses or employs a Pull mode.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="DestinationEndTo" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Separate To address for notice of abnormal subscription termination.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="Locale" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>If the events contain localized content, the service should accept a subscription with this Locale block acting as a hint. The language of the event message is encoded in an xml:lang attribute using RFC 3066 language codes. The service should attempt to localize any descriptive content to the specified language when delivering such events.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="ContentEncoding" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>This block acts as a hint to indicate how the delivered events should be encoded. The two standard tokens defined for this purpose are &quot;UTF-8&quot; or &quot;UTF-16&quot;, although other encoding formats may be specified if necessary.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="DeliveryMode" TYPE="uint16"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Method by which the service is to deliver events to the client. Values are as follows. Push (2): the event is sent to the destination address; depending on the protocol, delivery may not be guaranteed. PushWithAck (3): the service sends the event and waits for a specific acknowledgment message from the subscriber. Events (4): the service collects events into batches and sends the batches to the subscriber. Pull (5): the service collects the events into batches and the subscriber pulls each batch from the service using wxf:Pull.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ValueMap" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>2</VALUE><VALUE>3</VALUE><VALUE>4</VALUE><VALUE>5</VALUE><VALUE>..</VALUE><VALUE>32787..</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Values" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>Push</VALUE><VALUE>PushWithAck</VALUE><VALUE>Events</VALUE><VALUE>Pull</VALUE><VALUE>DMTF Reserved</VALUE><VALUE>Vendor Reserved</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="Heartbeat" TYPE="uint64"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Specifies how often heartbeat events are added to the event stream at the specified interval.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Units" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Seconds</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="SendBookmark" TYPE="boolean"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A property element that instructs the service to send a bookmark with each event. Bookmarks apply to all delivery modes. The bookmark is a token which represents an abstract pointer in the event stream, but whether it points to the last delivered event or the last event plus one (the upcoming event) makes no difference since the token is supplied to the same implementation during a subsequent wse:Subscribe operation. The service may thus attach any service-specific meaning and structure to the bookmark with no change to the client.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="MaxTime" TYPE="uint64"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>This element may contain a duration that indicates the maximum amount of time the service should allow to elapse while batching EVENT bodies. That is, this time may not be exceeded between the encoding of the first event in the batch and the dispatching of the batch for delivery.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Units" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Seconds</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="DeliveryAuth" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A URI identifying the WS-Management security profile to be used by the service (acting as publisher) when authenticating to the event sink (consumer) at event delivery time.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestinationWSManagement" PROPAGATED="false" NAME="PolyMorphismMode" TYPE="uint16"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Specifies the treatment of Indication subclasses, whether subclasses are to be included and with what set of properties. Valid values are: None, IncludeSubclassProperties, and ExcludeSubclassProperties. Using None, only instances of the parent class are included in the output (event stream). For other modes, subclass instances are included with the sets of properties stated.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ValueMap" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>1</VALUE><VALUE>2</VALUE><VALUE>3</VALUE><VALUE>..</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Values" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>None</VALUE><VALUE>IncludeSubclassProperties</VALUE><VALUE>ExcludeSubclassProperties</VALUE><VALUE>DMTF Reserved</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestination" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="SystemCreationClassName" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A System&apos;s CreationClassName. A CIM Listener destination is defined in context of a CIM_System (e.g., the sending system.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="MaxLen" TYPE="uint32"><VALUE>256</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestination" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="SystemName" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A System&apos;s Name. A CIM Listener destination is defined in context of a CIM_System (e.g., the sending system.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="MaxLen" TYPE="uint32"><VALUE>256</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestination" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="CreationClassName" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Indicates the name of the class or the subclass used in the creation of an instance. When used with the other key properties of this class, it allows all instances of this class and its subclasses to be uniquely identified.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="MaxLen" TYPE="uint32"><VALUE>256</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestination" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="Name" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER OVERRIDABLE="false" NAME="Key" TYPE="boolean"><VALUE>true</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Indicates the name of the CIM Listener destination.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="MaxLen" TYPE="uint32"><VALUE>256</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestination" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="PersistenceType" TYPE="uint16"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Describes the Persistence Type of the destination defined by this instance. If the value of PersistenceType is not specified, the value of PersistenceType MUST be treated as 2 (&quot;Permanent&quot;). A value of 2 (&quot;Permanent&quot;) declares that the destination is always expected to be available (e.g., system log file). Inability to access this destination MUST be treated as an error condition. A value of 3 (&quot;Transient&quot;) indicates that the destination is short-lived. Inability to access the destination MAY be treated as a normal termination condition. Subscriptions with &quot;Transient&quot; destinations MAY be deleted when the destination terminates or is no longer available.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ValueMap" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>1</VALUE><VALUE>2</VALUE><VALUE>3</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Values" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>Other</VALUE><VALUE>Permanent</VALUE><VALUE>Transient</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ModelCorrespondence" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>CIM_ListenerDestination.OtherPersistenceType</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestination" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="OtherPersistenceType" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A string describing (&quot;Other&quot;) values for PersistenceType. This value MUST be set to a non NULL value when the PersistenceType is 1 (&quot;Other&quot;). For all other values of PersistenceType, the value of OtherPersistenceType MUST be NULL.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ModelCorrespondence" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>CIM_ListenerDestination.PersistenceType</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestination" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="OtherProtocol" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A free-form string providing a description of the supported protocols when 1, &quot;Other&quot;, is specified for the Protocol.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ModelCorrespondence" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>CIM_ListenerDestination.Protocol</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ListenerDestination" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="Protocol" TYPE="uint16"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>Protocol describes an encoding and protocol which will be used to deliver the indication. If Other is used, the value for OtherProtocol must not be null.
If a protocol is not specified, 2 &quot;CIM-XML&quot; must be assumed.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ValueMap" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>1</VALUE><VALUE>2</VALUE><VALUE>3</VALUE><VALUE>4</VALUE><VALUE>5</VALUE><VALUE>6</VALUE><VALUE>..</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Values" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>Other</VALUE><VALUE>CIM-XML</VALUE><VALUE>SM CLP</VALUE><VALUE>WS-Management</VALUE><VALUE>WSDM</VALUE><VALUE>SMTP</VALUE><VALUE>DMTF Reserved</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="ModelCorrespondence" TYPE="string"><VALUE.ARRAY><VALUE>CIM_ListenerDestination.OtherProtocol</VALUE></VALUE.ARRAY></QUALIFIER><VALUE>2</VALUE></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ManagedElement" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="InstanceID" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>InstanceID is an optional property that may be used to opaquely and uniquely identify an instance of this class within the scope of the instantiating Namespace. Various subclasses of this class may override this property to make it required, or a key. Such subclasses may also modify the preferred algorithms for ensuring uniqueness that are defined below.
To ensure uniqueness within the NameSpace, the value of InstanceID should be constructed using the following &quot;preferred&quot; algorithm: 
&lt;OrgID&gt;:&lt;LocalID&gt; 
Where &lt;OrgID&gt; and &lt;LocalID&gt; are separated by a colon (:), and where &lt;OrgID&gt; must include a copyrighted, trademarked, or otherwise unique name that is owned by the business entity that is creating or defining the InstanceID or that is a registered ID assigned to the business entity by a recognized global authority. (This requirement is similar to the &lt;Schema Name&gt;_&lt;Class Name&gt; structure of Schema class names.) In addition, to ensure uniqueness, &lt;OrgID&gt; must not contain a colon (:). When using this algorithm, the first colon to appear in InstanceID must appear between &lt;OrgID&gt; and &lt;LocalID&gt;. 
&lt;LocalID&gt; is chosen by the business entity and should not be reused to identify different underlying (real-world) elements. If not null and the above &quot;preferred&quot; algorithm is not used, the defining entity must assure that the resulting InstanceID is not reused across any InstanceIDs produced by this or other providers for the NameSpace of this instance. 
If not set to null for DMTF-defined instances, the &quot;preferred&quot; algorithm must be used with the &lt;OrgID&gt; set to CIM.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ManagedElement" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="Caption" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The Caption property is a short textual description (one- line string) of the object.</VALUE></QUALIFIER><QUALIFIER NAME="MaxLen" TYPE="uint32"><VALUE>64</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ManagedElement" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>The Description property provides a textual description of the object.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY><PROPERTY CLASSORIGIN="CIM_ManagedElement" PROPAGATED="true" NAME="ElementName" TYPE="string"><QUALIFIER TRANSLATABLE="true" NAME="Description" TYPE="string"><VALUE>A user-friendly name for the object. This property allows each instance to define a user-friendly name in addition to its key properties, identity data, and description information. 
Note that the Name property of ManagedSystemElement is also defined as a user-friendly name. But, it is often subclassed to be a Key. It is not reasonable that the same property can convey both identity and a user-friendly name, without inconsistencies. Where Name exists and is not a Key (such as for instances of LogicalDevice), the same information can be present in both the Name and ElementName properties. Note that if there is an associated instance of CIM_EnabledLogicalElementCapabilities, restrictions on this properties may exist as defined in ElementNameMask and MaxElementNameLen properties defined in that class.</VALUE></QUALIFIER></PROPERTY></CLASS></VALUE.OBJECT></DECLGROUP></DECLARATION></CIM>
